<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aktivsens</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_community">Community</string>
    <string name="title_options">Options</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
        <![CDATA[
        <!DOCTYPE html>
<html>


<body>
    <h1>Privacy Policy</h1>
    <p>
        Welcome to our app! We value your privacy and want to be transparent about how we collect, use, and
        protect your data. This privacy policy explains what information we collect, how we use it, and your
        choices regarding your data.
    </p>

    <h2>Registration</h2>
    <p>
        Our registration process requires you to provide only a username and password of your choice. We do not
        require any email, phone number, or other personal sensitive information.
    </p>

    <h2>Data Collection</h2>
    <p>
        We only collect movement counts and dates. We do not collect any location data or personal information.
        We do not store any sensitive information about you.
    </p>

    <h2>Data Storage</h2>
    <p>
        Please note that data collected is not encrypted and is stored in a public database. However, we take
        all reasonable precautions to protect your data and ensure its security.
    </p>

    <h2>Data Deletion</h2>
    <p>
        If you choose to delete your account, all records associated with your username will be entirely deleted
        from our database. We do not retain any of your data after account deletion.
    </p>

    <h2>Contact Us</h2>
    <p>
        If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy or the use of your data, please feel free
        to contact us at <a href="mailto:deveyra.j.bsinfotech@gmail.com">deveyra.j.bsinfotech@gmail.com</a>.
    </p>

    <p>
        Thank you for trusting us with your data. Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to
        protecting it.
    </p>
</body>

</html>

        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>

